whatpulse.org 2019-06-14

# Privacy Policy | WhatPulse

The following page outlines how WhatPulse uses and protects any information that you give WhatPulse when using this website or the software client.

WhatPulse is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. WhatPulse may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. By using any services of WhatPulse you agree to this privacy policy.

##### Information Collected

WhatPulse only collects information (be it via a website form or the software client) that is relevant to the purpose of our website. When you register for a WhatPulse account, we will ask you for your name (as provided) and valid e-mail address. 

The software client collects statistics from your computer(s) as you direct it too. The types of statistics can vary and you have the ability to turn off each individual type of statistic. When you 'pulse' to our website, the software client will only send the data you have allowed it to send.

The information collected with the WhatPulse client is only used for analytics as shown on the website. Information linked to your account will never be sold or handed over to a third party. Only aggregated, anonymized data may be used for global analytics by third parties, on-site advertisements or marketing purposes.

_In summary,_

We collect relevant information so you can participate in our website. You have complete control what statistics are gathered. We don't sell your personal information and stats.

##### Keeping Information Safe

Your WhatPulse account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. This password is stored encrypted. Protect against unauthorized access to your account by logging off the website once you have finished using a shared computer.

Only WhatPulse staff who need personal information to perform a specific task (upon your request) are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security policies.

_In summary,_

Your account is protected by a password. We encrypt it, you must also keep it secure. Our staff may access your account only to do a specific (requested) task.

##### Policy Towards Children

You must be 13 or older to register a WhatPulse account. If you become aware that your child has provided WhatPulse with personal information without your consent, please contact us at [privacy@whatpulse.org](mailto:privacy@whatpulse.org). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information without parental consent, we will take steps to remove such information. 

_In summary,_

We allow 13 years and older. If you are younger than 18 years of age, please ask your parent for consent.

##### Effective Date of this Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is effective as of 22 December, 2012.

_In summary,_

Effective as of December 10, 2014.
